How's the blind date?
كيف صورتك
He looks good.
أعتقد أنه يبدو جيدًا
But
نعم
he lacks a bit of manliness.
ينقصنا بعض الشجاعة
What about yours?
ماذا عنك؟
Nice.
ممكن
The wedding ceremony begins.
حفل الزواج يبدأ
Diqiu, let's swap.
سأبدل الأرض معك
No.
لا
Wei Xing is good-looking.
‫النجوم جميلة
You're the ugly ones.
أنتم قبيحون
I'll marry Shi Wenke.
سأتزوج مع شي وين كي
That's great.
هذا رائع
Shi Wenke, you do it.
شي وين كه، تعال
No.
لا أريد
Be careful.
احذري
The marriage license got wet.
بطاقة الزواج مبللة
I'm going to get hit by my mom again today.
اليوم سوف تتعرض للضرب من قبل أمي
I stole the marriage certificate
لقد سرقت شهادة الزواج
behind my parents' back.
سرا
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعلون؟
Now,
الجميع الآن
take a look at the blackboard.
ألقوا نظرة على اللوح
Read it quietly.
اقرأها بصوت منخفض
Wang Huanyu, what's wrong?
ما هو؟ وانغ تشى يو ماذا حدث
Ms. Wu.
أستاذ وو
Speaking English in this classroom.
‫speaking‬ ‫في الواقع‬ ألمس ألمس يجب أن تتحدث الإنجليزية في هذا الفصل
I'm not good at speaking.
‫لغتي ليست جيدة‬
Guo Ting.
قوه تينغ
Zhao Heng!
تشاو هنغ
Stand up.
قف
What makes you so happy?
ما الذي تفعله so happy ما الذي يجعلك سعيدة هكذا
We are laughing at
we are laughing ♪ at نحن نضحك ♪
Wang Diqiu.
‫وانغ الأرض‬
Because he is
♪ because he is a ♪ لأنه
a handsome boy.
فتى وسيم
Let it pass.
هيا ارقص هذا
Read this.
اقرأ هذا
The...
هذا
astrolabe.
‫ astrolabe  لوحة النجوم
tetrometer
جهاز الأربع
and...
and
This one.
هذا
In our life,
in our life في حياتنا
we will be nice to other people.
we will be nice في حياتنا سنكون جيدين مع الآخرين
Go on.
لنواصل
And you, Guo Ting?
وأنت
When facing our
ما هو وجها لوجه
Parents,
parents  والداي
We are
نحن
What?
ماذا؟
And...
and
Go on.
استمر
Zhao Heng.
تشاو هينج
Forget it.
انسي الأمر
Sit down.
اجلسوا
Thank you.
شكرا
Good job, honey.
‫شكراً لك يا عزيزتي‬
These grapes are especially sweet.
هذه المسطرة حلوة جدا
Thank you, Auntie.
شكراً لك يا عمتي
Is it for you?
هل هذا لك
If he dares to be absent,
إذا تجرأ على إهمال
tell me.
أخبرني
I'll beat him to death.
سأقتله
Mom.
أمي
It doesn't have to be like that.
لا أعتقد ذلك
Am I still your son?
هل ما زلت ابنك
What do you think?
ما رأيك
Don't worry, Auntie.
اطمئني يا عمتي
He's fine.
إنه بخير
OK.
حسناً
Study hard.
تعلموا جيدا
Call me if you're thirsty or hungry.
إذا كنت عطشان نادوني
I'm leaving.
حسناً سأغادر
Why does my mom treat you and me differently?
لماذا أمي تعاملك معي وجهان
Eat after you finish.
تناولي بعد الانتهاء
Is it funny?
هل هذا مضحك
No.
لا
Wang Diqiu.
‫وانغ الأرض‬
Isn't it cute?
‫لطيفة أليس كذلك‬
Enjoy yourself!
تلعب بنفسك
Wei Xing!
‫وي شينغ
Don't go.
لا تذهب
You've been taking me home every night.
يرجى توصيلي كل ليلة
It's okay.
لا بأس
It's dangerous to walk at night.
الطريق في الليل خطير
It'll be nice when the streetlights are fixed.
انتظر حتى يتم إصلاح المصباح
Give it to me.
أعطني
I think
أشعر
you are in a good mood recently.
أنت في مزاج جيد مؤخرًا
Really?
حقا
The corners
هذا لك
of your mouth.
زاوية فمك
Maybe it's because
ربما بسبب
the family atmosphere is good recently.
الجو العائلي جيد مؤخرًا
That's good.
جيد جدا
Wenwen.
ون ون
Look what's over there.
انظر ماذا هناك
Wei Xing.
‫vệ tinh‬
I'm coming.
‫أنا قادم
Thanks.
‫وي شينغ شكراً
Thank you, Wei Xing.
‫شكراً لك
Let's go.
لنذهب
Is
‫وي شينغ
Is Wei Xing angry?
هل أنت غاضب؟
Take out the question mark.
تخلص من هذا؟
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
What happened last night?
ماذا حدث الليلة الماضية؟
I've never seen you so angry.
لم أرك تغضب هكذا من قبل
Nothing.
لا شيء
I just never thought
لم أفكر قط
he would do that to me.
أنه يجرؤ على معاملتي هكذا
How dare he?
كيف يجرؤ على معاملتك هكذا
Wei Xing.
وي شينغ
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به
This is so exciting!
هذا مثير جدا
Go ahead!
هيا
You're so good at coaxing Guo Ting.
أنت عادة لا تغضبين قوه تينغ
That's Tingting.
تلك تينغ تينغ
Wei Xing is not easy to be fooled.
‫هل من السهل خداع النجوم
Besides,
علاوة على ذلك
I've never seen her angry.
لم أر النجوم تغضب من قبل
I'm a little scared.
أنا خائفة قليلا
It's your fault for being perfunctory with her.
‫من طلب منك أن تتصرف بلطف
Wei Xing usually seems gentle and soft,
‫يبدو وي شينغ لطيفًا عادةً
but she's actually very serious.
لكنها في الواقع جادة جدا
Think about it.
‫فكري‬
It's so hard to learn dancing.
‫تتعلم الرقص صعب جدا‬
She can endure it.
‫يمكنها الصمود‬
The only way you can do now
الطريقة الوحيدة
is to get in the attitude of admitting you're wrong.
هو وضع موقفك في الاعتراف بالذنب
I'm going to practice.
سأتدرب على الرقص
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ‬
Oh no.
يا إلهي
Got it.
فهمت
Good luck.
هيا
It's fixed.
حسنا
When it's broken,
لا تسمع الكلام
Just hit it.
فقط اضربه
I feel
أشعر
Wei Xing is surrounded by dark air.
‫أن الجو الأسود محيط بجانب النجوم
The timing is wrong.
الوقت غير صحيح
Next time.
تعال مرة أخرى
I agree.
موافقة لا مثيل لها
Let's go.
هيا هيا
Don't you have night self-learning classes?
أليس لديك دروس ليلي الليلة؟
Why do you go home and get changed?
لماذا عدت إلى المنزل لتغيير ملابسك
Of course I have to dress up when shopping.
بالطبع يجب ارتداء ملابس جميلة للتسوق
I don't understand girls like you.
لا أفهم الفتيات
Girls are a pain in the ass.
‫هل الفتيات مزعجات جداً ما العمل‬
Fine.
حسنا
Let's go on a
إذًا اليوم
shopping spree today.
التسوق بشكل جنوني
OK?
حسناً؟
Let's go.
لنذهب
This is often out of stock.
غالبا ما ينقصنا البضائع
Buy more.
يجب أن أشتري المزيد من هذا
Two bottles.
زجاجتين
And this shower gel.
‫خذ زجاجة أخرى من طلاء الاستحمام‬
I'll bring two bottles for my mom.
سأحضر زجاجتين لأمي أيضا
Okay.
حسنا حسنا
That's enough.
يكفي يكفي
Let's go.
لنذهب
I like this.
أحب هذا
Take two bottles.
خذ زجاجتين
Two bottles?
ماذا تأخذين زجاجتين
Just move two boxes.
فقط نقل صندوقين
You are so nice.
هذا جيد
Ms. Jin.
سيدة جين تشي
Tingting is here.
تينغ تينغ هنا
Mom.
أمي
Hurry up. Give it to me.
بسرعة بسرعة أعطني
Put it here.
ضعها هنا ضعها هنا
Come on.
تعال تعال
It's heavy.
ثقيل جدا
Ms. Jin, we're hungry.
سيدة جين تشي نحن جائع
I want braised pork.
نريد اللحم المطهو ببطء
I'll cook for you now.
سأطبخ لك الآن
I need to go to the toilet.
سأذهب إلى الحمام
Son.
بني
Where's your dad?
أين والدك؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف
He hasn't been here these days.
لم يأت إلى هنا هذه الأيام
He hasn't come to eat for days.
لم يأتي لتناول الطعام منذ عدة أيام
But you know well, it's not surprising
لكن أنت تعرف أن والدك
that your dad is like this
عندما يكون العمل مشغولًا
when he's busy with his business.
هذا ليس غريبًا
Mom,
أمي
Do you think
أخبريني
dad is having an affair?
هل يوجد أحد في الخارج؟
It's none of my business.
ما علاقة ذلك بي
He'd better find someone quickly
من الأفضل أن يجد
before he gets old and miserable
حتى لا يكون كبار السن مأساويًا
with no one to take care of him.
لا يوجد شخص يتبول
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
I checked dad's underwear for you.
لقد فحصت ملابس أبي الداخلية لك
None of them is missing.
لم تفقد واحدة
How dare you make fun of me?
كيف تجرؤ على خداعي؟
- I’m scared. I’m scared. - What’s wrong?
أنا خائف
What's wrong?
ماذا حدث
Nothing.
لا بأس لا بأس
I'll make braised pork for you.
سأذهب لأحضر لك لحم الخنزير المطهو ببطء
Sure.
حسنا حسنا
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
It's none of your business.
ليس من شأنك
No big deal.
ما مدهش
Happy birthday.
عيد ميلاد سعيد عيد ميلاد سعيد
Make a wish.
أمنية أمنية
Wait.
انتظر
Make a wish
تمني
to get into Peking University.
أن تنجح بجامعة بكين
Okay.
حسنا حسنا
Make your wish.
تقرر الأمنية بنفسك
Go to Peking University.
‏يمكنك دخول جامعة (بكين)‏
Go to Peking University!
وألتحق بجامعة بكين
Done.
لقد تمنيت
Blow out the candles.
انفخ الشمعة
I prepared a birthday gift for you.
لقد أعددت لك هدية عيد ميلاد
Look.
انظر
I
أمك
went to a lot of bookstores
ذهبت إلى العديد من المكتبات للبحث عنها
to handpick them.
اخترت كل شيء
Do it well.
اعمل بجد
Don't fool me.
لا تخدعني
It'll help
إنه مفيد
improve your grades.
في تحسين النتائج
Do you hear me?
هل سمعت
There's more.
ماذا أيضاً؟
Jingjing knew your birthday
جينج جينج تعرف عيد ميلادك
and sent a gift in advance.
من أجل عيد ميلادك
From my sister?
أرسلتها الأخت
Yes.
نعم
Open it and see what it is.
افتحه وانظر ما هو
I'll open it.
سأفكه
Wall calendar for the examination.
لقد فشلت في امتحان القبول الجامعي
This is a good gift.
‫لقد أرسلت هذه الهدية بشكل جيد‬
How thoughtful.
كم أنتِ مهتمة
She cares about her sister's college entrance examination .
أنا مهتمة جداً بشأن امتحان القبول الجامعي
Jingjing has always been a student council officer in school
شينج جينج كانت دائمًا قائدة اتحاد الطلبة
and won scholarships every year.
حصل على منحة كل عام
But you're too demanding for your children.
لكن متطلباتك تجاه الأطفال عالية جدا
If I didn't ask her so much,
إذا لم يكن لدي متطلبات عالية للطفل
would she have gotten into a major university?
يمكنها دخول الجامعة الرئيسية
Okay.
حسنا حسنا
Give her a call.
اتصل بالطفل
Praise her.
مدح
By the way, let her say happy birthday to Wenwen.
وأطلب منها أن تقول كلمة عيد ميلاد سعيد لـ ون ون
Hello.
ألو
I'm your mother.
أنا أمك
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
In the library?
في المكتبة
I'm going to say something too.
سأذهب للتحدث
Sort out the information of the debate?
تنظيم بيانات المناظرة
Well.
حسنا حسنا
I wanted to tell you something about
أردت أن أقول لك
how happy your sister was
أن أختك حصلت على هدية عيد ميلادك
to get your birthday present.
سعيدة جدا
And asked you to say happy birthday to her.
أريدك أن تقول لها عيد ميلاد سعيد
Since you are so busy,
بما أنك مشغول جدا
I won't waste any time.
فلا تضيع الوقت
Let me say something.
دعني أقول بضع كلمات
- Come on. - Don’t waste time.
تعال لا تضيع الوقت
Okay.
حسنًا حسنًا
Take care.
اعتني بنفسك
Alright.
حسنا
Don't waste time.
لا تضيع الوقت
Don't listen to his nagging.
لا تستمعي إلى ثرثرته
Take the time to study.
‏أسرعي في الدراسة‏
Let me know when you get your grades.
‏أخبريني‏
Sister.
أختي
Wenwen.
ون ون
Your call.
هاتفك
Coming.
مرحباً.
Hello.
ألو
Shi Wenke.
شي وين كي
Why did you call me?
لماذا اتصلت بي
I...
أنا
I don't know a question.
لدي سؤال لا أفهمه
I want to discuss with you.
أريد أن أناقش معك
Now?
الآن؟
Must it be tonight?
هل يجب أن تكون الليلة؟
I'll wait for you at the bookstore.
سأنتظرك في المكتبة
You must come.
يجب أن تأتي
Shi Wenke.
التاريخ
What did Shi Wenke want from you?
ما الأمر؟
He asked me to study at the bookstore.
‏طلب مني أن أذهب إلى المكتبة‏
Is it Shi Wenke who ranked second in the grade?
‏هل هو التاريخ الذي حصل على المركز الثاني في الصف؟‏
He asked you to study?
هل طلب منك أن تحل الأسئلة؟
Yes.
نعم
Okay.
حسنا
Hurry up and go.
اذهب بسرعة
Go. I'll wait for you at home.
بسرعة سأنتظرك في المنزل
Shi Wenke.
التاريخ
Happy birthday!
عيد ميلاد سعيد
Thank you.
شكرا لكم جميعا
Wenwen.
ون ون
We guess you had cake at home.
خمن أنك تناولت الكعكة في المنزل
so
لذلك
we made this.
‫صنعت هذا‬
He made it.
‫هو طبخ‬
Thank you.
شكرا
Wenwen.
ون ون
Your gift.
هديتك
This is mine.
هذا لي
So many.
الكثير
Thank you.
شكراً لكم جميعاً
Should we pretend
هل نتظاهر
blow out the candles and make a wish?
أن تطفئ الشموع وتتمنى أمنية
Sure.
حسنا
Light the candles.
أشعل النار أشعل النار
One.
واحد
Two.
اثنان
Three.
ثلاثة
Take a seat.
تفضلوا بالجلوس
I'll get you some snacks.
سأحضر لكم وجبات خفيفة
[Shizai Bookstore]
حسنا حسنا
Shall we pour it on the table?
هل يمكننا أن نسكب على الطاولة؟
Do you want this?
هل تريدين هذا؟
I want to eat this.
أريد هذا
Eat this.
تناولي هذا
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ‬
Thanks.
شكرا
Take Tingting away for me.
ساعدني في أخذ تينغ تينغ
Have you figured out a way?
هل وجدت طريقة
Hurry up.
بسرعة
OK.
حسنا
I'll do my best.
اذهب إلى جبل السيف والطهو
I'm so good to you.
ليس لدي ما أقوله
Wait.
انتظر.
Remember to tell Uncle Wei.
تذكر أن تخبر السيد وي.
Okay.
حسنا.
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به
Just say it.
قل ما تريد
Wei Xing is not an outsider.
النجوم ليست غريبة
I can only tell you.
يمكنني فقط أن أخبرك
Just me?
هل أنت بمفردك؟
OK.
حسنا.
Wei Xing, I have something to do with Han Shuai.
وي شينغ، لدي شيء مع القائد هان.
You and Wang go home first.
يمكنك العودة مع لاو وانغ
What do you want to tell me?
ماذا تريد أن تقول لي
You'll know soon.
ستعرفين بعد قليل
Let me know a little bit first.
‫سأخبره قليلا‬
Please.
أرجوك
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به
Wenwen.
ون ون
When I was on the phone,
عندما اتصلت بك للتو
you sounded a little upset.
عندما اتصلت بك
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
Nothing.
لا شيء
It's about my sister.
إنه أمر أختي
Your sister?
أختك
What's wrong with her?
ماذا بها؟
Mom.
أمي
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Aren't you working problems here?
ألم تقومي بتحضير الأسئلة هنا؟
Why are you playing here?
لماذا تلعب هنا؟
I thought it was hard for you to study here.
ظننت أنك تتعلم بجد هنا
I brought you fruits.
أحضرت الفاكهة لكما
But you two are playing here.
والنتيجة أنتما تلعبان هنا
Say something.
تكلم
I...
أنا
What?
أنا أنا ماذا أنا
Auntie, let me explain.
عمتي دعيني أشرح لك
Explain what?
ماذا تشرح
The good kid who got second in the grade
‫طفل جيد في الصف الثاني
actually called specifically to lie.
‫حتى يتصل بكذب
I've come to see that
فهمت
academic performance has little to do
إن نتيجة الدراسة
with character.
لا علاقة له به
Auntie,
خالتي
I apologize.
أعتذر لك
Don't blame Wenwen.
لا تلومي ون ون
Let's go home.
لنعود للمنزل
Wenwen.
ون ون
Hurry up.
بسرعة
What do you want to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
Tell me.
قل بسرعة
Just wait.
انتظر قليلا
I'm so worried.
أنا قلقة للغاية
Tell me.
قل بسرعة
Please, please.
أرجوك
Please tell me. Please.
أخبرني أرجوك
Well,
إذن
close your eyes first.
أغلقي عينيك أولا
No way.
مستحيل
Is it this?
هل هذا هو؟
Han Shuai,
سيد هان
Wait and see.
انتظر
Ultraman.
أوترامان
Mom.
أمي
Shi Wenke did it to celebrate my birthday.
التاريخ لكنه احتفل بعيد ميلادي
He meant well.
إنه لطيف
Didn't you celebrate your birthday?
ألم تحتفل بعيد ميلاده؟
I think you're just playful.
أعتقد أنك طموح
I couldn't listen to Mr. Chen
لا يمكنني معاملتك بشكل جيد
to be nice to you.
أستمع إلى السيد تشين
I should have strictly
يجب أن أفعل ما طلبته
according to my original requirements.
متطلباتي الأصلية
I see.
فهمت
How about this?
هكذا
We'll talk in the office later.
سنتحدث في الشركة بعد قليل
Okay.
حسنا
Dad.
أبي
By the way,
صحيح
Shuaishuai.
وسيم وسيم
I'm busy in the company these days.
أبي مشغول في الشركة هذه الأيام
Leave the money
ضع المال
here.
ضعه هنا
Take care of yourself these days.
اعتني بنفسك هذه الأيام
Buy whatever you want.
اشتري ما تريدين أن تأكلي
Dad, wait.
أبي انتظر
Xu Yuteng's concert will be on sale soon.
سيبيع تذكرة الحفل الغنائي لـ شو يي تنغ بعد يومين
I want to take my friends to have fun.
أريد أن آخذكم للعب
Get me six tickets.
‫ساعدني في الحصول على ستة تذاكر‬
The first row.
ثم أريد موقع الصف الأول
OK.
حسناً
I'll ask them to arrange it in the office.
سأطلب منهم الترتيب في المكتب بعد قليل
I'll do it when I have time.
سأساعدك في القيام بذلك عندما يكون لديك وقت
Tingting.
تينغ تينغ
Where is Diqiu?
أين الأرض
He went to school so early?
لقد ذهب إلى المدرسة في وقت مبكر
He went to school early in the morning.
ذهب إلى المدرسة في الصباح الباكر
Wei Xing is monitoring him every day.
الآن وي شينغ يراقبه كل يوم
He is very serious.
إنه جاد جدا
That's great.
حسنا
I'm going to school.
سأذهب إلى المدرسة
Goodbye, aunt.
مع السلامة يا عمتي
Take care.
على مهلك
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
Look.
انظر
So many swans.
الكثير من الأوزة
The cold Siberian winds have been blowing all season.
♫ تهب الرياح الباردة الموسم ♫
The swans
الإوزة ليست بعيدة عن آلاف الأميال
migrate here to spend the winter.
انتقلوا إلى هنا لقضاء الشتاء
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
The swans
أيها الإوزة
can overcome all difficulties and come here.
‫يمكن استبعاد جميع الصعوبات‬
I think
أعتقد
I should learn from them.
يجب أن أتعلم منهم
No matter in life
بغض النظر عن الحياة
or studying,
أو في الدراسة
I should correct my attitude.
يجب أن أكون في موقفي الصحيح
Wei Xing, I was wrong.
‫وي شينغ أنا مخطئ
I'll study hard from now on.
سأعمل بجد في المستقبل
♫Where should I go?♫
لن أفعل شيئًا صغيرًا
How could you say that?
يمكنك قول هذا
That's with the help of Han Shuai and Shi Wenke, of course.
بالطبع هناك فرشاة بين الوسيم والتاريخ
Okay.
حسناً
Then
إذن
I'll trust you again.
سأثق بك مرة أخرى
♫Wind blows the sand around me.♫
حقاً؟
Yes.
نعم
♫I want to take you to the end of the world.♫
‏شكراً لكم‏
Of course, I wrote the manuscript myself.
بالطبع، كتبت المخطوطة بنفسي
No one will believe.
لا أصدق ذلك
It's true.
حقا
I'd be a puppy if I lied to you.
كذب عليك كلب
I should have brought some food.
لو كنت أعلم أنني أحضرت بعض الطعام
Give me your hand.
مد يدك
You really prepared!
أنت حقاً مستعدة -نعم -
Feed it.
ألو
Wenwen.
ون ون
Is Auntie still angry?
هل ما زلت غاضبة
It's okay.
لا بأس
It was late that day.
لقد عدت متأخرا في ذلك اليوم
My mom...
أمي
She didn't say anything.
لم تقل أي شيء
Then...
إذًا
Auntie...
عمتي
I'm looking for Wei Xing.
أبحث عن vệ tinh
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
Guo Ting is looking for you.
قوه تينغ تبحث عنك
Go.
اذهب بسرعة
Wenwen.
ون ون
Bye.
مع السلامة
You want to see me?
ما الأمر؟
Why are you so sleepy?
لماذا تشعر بالنعاس
Diqiu also slept in the classroom for a day.
لقد نمت الأرض في الفصل طوال اليوم
Don't mention it.
لا تذكري ذلك
I didn't sleep well last night.
لم أنم جيدا طوال الليل
You and Diqiu didn't sleep well last night.
لم تنامي جيداً مع الأرض طوال الليل
Lower your voice.
اخفضي صوتك
Come here and talk.
تعال وتحدث
Don't think too much.
توقف عن التفكير
I spent the night at the lake
كنت معه بجانب البحيرة
with him watching the swans.
طوال الليل
Don't think too much.
لا تفكر كثيرا
Look at the swan.
انظر إلى البجعة
I'm angry that he didn't study hard.
أنا فقط أغضبه لأنه لا يتعلم بجد
Don't think too much.
لا تنشر الأفكار مرة أخرى
Stop.
توقف
What's wrong?
ما بك
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
Let me ask you something.
أريد أن أسألك شيئا
Go ahead.
تكلم
I just want to ask...
أريد فقط أن أسأل
Is it what I think?
هل هذا ما أفكر به؟
Is it really what I think?
حقاً كما كنت أفكر
You have no idea how suffocating I am these days.
أنت لا تعرف أنني أخنق كثيرا هذه الأيام
Lower your voice.
أخفض صوتك
Let me tell you.
أقول لك
No one knows besides you and me.
لا أحد يعرف هذا
We can't let anyone else know.
لا يمكن أن يعرف الشخص الثالث مرة أخرى
I swear
أقسم
I won't let anyone know.
لن أسمح لأحد أن يعرف
Otherwise,
وإلا
I...
أنا
If you break your promise,
إذا خالفتها
all the idols you follow will have bad luck,
سيبرد جميع المعبود
all the albums you buy will be bootlegs,
كل الألبوم التي اشتريتها مزيفة
and all the novels you read will be tragedies.
الرواية التي قرأتها كلها مأساوية
This oath is too cruel.
هذا القسم قاس للغاية
Swear it now.
أقسم بسرعة
OK.
حسناً
I swear
أقسم
I won't let anyone else know.
لن أسمح لأحد أن يعرف
Or I’ll…
وإلا
Han Shuai.
سيد هان
I swear too.
أقسم أيضا
Tingting!
تينغ تينغ
I'm innocent!
أنا مظلومة
I didn't ask him to eavesdrop.
لم أطلب منه أن يسترق السمع
I'm sure of it.
أعدك بذلك
I just happened to pass by.
لقد مررت بهذا الطريق
Wei Xing, don't worry.
‫لا تقلق
I'm much cautious with my words than her.
فمي أكثر صرامة منها
I will never tell anyone.
لن أخبر أحداً
What are you talking about?
ماذا تقول؟
I won't tell anyone
سر النجوم
even if I had to swallow it.
‫لن أخبر أحد حتى لو ابتلعته في بطني
With your mouth,
فمك
can you swallow it?
هل يمكنك ابتلاعه؟
How about a bet?
وإلا أراهن
Anyone who says it will be
إذا قال أحد
another man's servant for a week.
سيكون خادم شخص آخر لمدة أسبوع
Fine.
سأفعل
- The curse cannot be broken.
لا يمكن كسر التعويذة
Take a bet on me.
أراهنني
You two are really something.
أنتما الاثنان
Go back to class.
عد إلى الدرس
I won't tell anyone.
لن أقول ذلك
Director.
أيها المدير
This is Jianmin.
أنا جيان مين
Dad, you're home early today.
لقد عدت باكراً اليوم
Mr. Han,
المدير هان
I'm not urging you.
أنا لم أحثك
I have no choice.
لا يمكنني فعل أي شيء
You know your sister-in-law.
أنت تعرف أخوتك
If I don't get the money back today,
إذا لم أستطع استعادة المال اليوم
I won't be able to explain.
لن أستطيع أن أشرح ذلك بعد عودتي
Yeah.
نعم
I lent you money before,
لقد أقرضتك المال من قبل
and you said you'd pay it back in a month,
اتفقنا على شهر
and then a couple months went by,
الآن شهر أو شهر آخر
I can't wait anymore.
لا أستطيع الانتظار
I've been
أما عن المال
trying to figure out the money.
كنت أفكر في طريقة
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
For the sake of our years of friendship,
من أجل صداقتنا لسنوات عديدة
you
أنتم
go back first.
ارجعوا أولا
My son is going home.
سيعود ابني إلى المنزل
Shuaishuai is back.
لقد عاد وسيم وسيم
We...
نحن
We're talking to your dad.
نحن نتحدث عن شيء مع والدك
Shuaishuai.
وسيم وسيم
It's okay.
لا بأس
Go back to your room.
عودي إلى غرفتك
Dad.
أبي
I heard everything.
لقد سمعت كل شيء
Uncle Luo.
العم لوه
Uncle Li. Uncle Lin.
العم لي العم لين
Although I don't know much about business,
على الرغم من أنني لا أفهم الكثير عن العمل
my dad has always kept his promise.
لكن أبي دائماً يحتفظ بوعده
So,
لذلك
I hope
آمل
you can trust him one more time.
أن تثقوا به مرة أخرى
One month.
شهر
Give me one more month.
أمهلني شهر آخر
I'll pay you back
سأبيع كل شيء
with everything I have.
سأعيدها لكم
OK?
ممكن؟
Fine.
حسنا
Since
طالما
Mr. Han
المدير هان
made such a promise in front of his son.
لقد وعدته أمام ابني
Trust him one more time.
ثق به مرة أخرى
OK?
ممكن؟
Sure.
حسنا
Take care.
مع السلامة
Dad.
أبي
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
لماذا لم تخبرني مبكرا
I've grown up.
لقد كبرت
You're still carrying a backpack.
ما زلت أحمل حقيبتي
You haven't graduated yet.
لم تخرج بعد
How's that for growing up?
كيف كبرت
You also
ألست كذلك
went out to work at my age
ذهبت للعمل في هذا العمر
and met my mom.
قابلت أمي
I thought I could make it through.
كنت أظن أنني أستطيع التحمل
In the past,
في الماضي
I started from scratch with your mother.
بدأت مع والدتك باليد الأبيض
We've experienced all kinds of hardships.
لقد رأيت الكثير من الصعاب
It's all about thinking and doing things.
يعتمد على الشجاعة والشجاعة
I didn't expect the international situation
لم أتوقع أن الوضع الدولي الآن
has such a great influence on trade.
تأثير كبير على التجارة
I lost money soon,
ستخسر أموالي قريبا
then borrowed
ثم اقترضها
and lost it again.
خسرنا مرة أخرى
Again and again.
‫اقترضت مرة أخرى وخسر مرة أخرى‬
All the money I earned before is gone.
كل المال الذي كسبته من قبل قد ضاع
Dad.
أبي
Cheer up.
ابتهج
Don't worry,
ألم أقل
there's still a month left.
لا يزال هناك شهر
I believe you.
أنا أثق بك
you can handle it.
يمكنك التعامل معها بالتأكيد
Fine.
حسنا
With your words,
‫بوجودك هذه الجملة
I'm full of energy.
أبيك مليء بالحيوية
By the way,
صحيح
don't tell your mom
لا تخبر والدتك
to save her nagging.
لا تثرثر
Don't worry, dad.
لا تقلق يا أبي
I won't let her worry about us.
لن أجعلها تقلق بشأننا
Tell you the truth.
قل الحقيقة
I feel much better.
أشعر بتحسن كبير
Then I...
أنا
make you
تفضلي
a bowl of instant noodles
أحضر وعاء من المعكرونة سريعة التحضير
Okay.
حسنا
Wait for it.
انتظر
Director.
أيها المدير
Jianmin.
جيان مين
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
I need to go out.
يجب أن أخرج
It's about work.
الأمر يتعلق بالعمل
Don't you trust me?
ألست مطمئنًا بشأن عملي؟
I'm in a hurry to leave.
أنا في عجلة من أمري
What about the list?
ماذا عن القائمة؟
You flipped my desk!
أنت تفتح طاولتي
I didn't.
لم أفحصها من قبل
I saw it when I was delivering apples.
رأيت عندما أرسلت التفاحة
Wang Jianmin.
وانج جيان مين
I'm telling you this today.
سأقول لك هذا الكلام اليوم
There's nothing I can do about the factory redeployment.
ليس لدي خيار في نقل المصنع
You don't have to come to work tomorrow.
لا داعي أن تأتي للعمل غدا
You took my money.
هل أخذت أموالي
What are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء
You can eat whatever you want.
يمكنك تناول الطعام بشكل عشوائي
Don't talk nonsense.
لا يمكنك قول هذا بشكل عشوائي
I'm telling the truth.
أنا أقول الحقيقة
What truth?
أي حقيقة
No one else came to ask for it
لا أحد يريد
but you.
أنت فقط تريد
Wang.
لاو وانغ
You've got to be smart.
انتبه
Others?
الآخرون